<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
	<PrisonLabor_Indroduction.label>Zwangsarbeit für Gefangene</PrisonLabor_Indroduction.label>
	<PrisonLabor_Indroduction.helpText>Du kannst Gefangene zum Arbeiten zwingen.\n\nUm dies zu tun, musst du "Zur Arbeit zwingen" im Bereich "Gefangene" auswählen.\n\nGefangene werden Aufgaben im erlaubten Gebiet erledigen. Stelle sicher dass die ihre Aufgaben erreichen können.\n\nSie können nur kochen, minern, Waldarbeiten erledigen, tragen, säubern oder Pflanzen anbauen die keine Fähigkeiten benötigen.\n\nGefangene verweigern manchmal die Arbeit. Die Gründe dafür können unterschiedlich sein. Sie können verwundet, hungrig, müde oder nicht ausreichend motiviert sein.\n\nTipp: Du kannst Arbeiten im "Arbeit"-Tab zuweisen.\n\Tipp: Wenn du eine Kochstelle in eine Gefängniszelle stellst, stelle sicher dass die rohe Nahrung erreichen können.\n\nTipp: Du kannst Gefangenen erlauben durch Türen zu gehen wenn du sie offen stehen lässt.</PrisonLabor_Indroduction.helpText>

	<PrisonLabor_Motivation.label>Motivating prisoners</PrisonLabor_Motivation.label>
	<PrisonLabor_Motivation.helpText>One of yours prisoners stopped working.\nHe won't work any longer, unless he gets motivated.\n\nYou can check status of motivation in "Needs" tab.\n\nMake sure you have enough wardens (check "Work" tab), or draft one of your colonist and order him to stand around your prisoners.\n\nLow motivation of prisoners can lead to revolts.</PrisonLabor_Motivation.helpText>

	<PrisonLabor_Growing.label>Growing by prisoners</PrisonLabor_Growing.label>
	<PrisonLabor_Growing.helpText>Prisoners can only grow plants that don't require any special skills like potato or cotton. They can however gather any plant that is ordered to harvest.</PrisonLabor_Growing.helpText>

	<PrisonLabor_Management.label>Prison labor management</PrisonLabor_Management.label>
	<PrisonLabor_Management.helpText>You can manage your prison labor in several ways.\n\nYou can assign work types to prisoners by accessing "Work" tab.\n\nYou can restrict when prisoners should work, rest, or sleep by accessing "Restrict" tab.\n\nYou can restrict work to "Prisoners only". For work orders that covers area you can choose "Labor area" tool from "Architect"->"Orders" panel.\nFor bills there is an option "Prisoners only".</PrisonLabor_Management.helpText>

	<PrisonLabor_Timetable.label>Prisoners time restrictions</PrisonLabor_Timetable.label>
	<PrisonLabor_Timetable.helpText>You can make time restrictions for prisoners.\n\n"Work" time will force them to work even when they're hungry or tired.\n\n"Joy" time will let them rest from job and get motivation bonus.\n\n"Sleep" time will force them to stay in prison cell.\n\n"Anything" is default setting.</PrisonLabor_Timetable.helpText>
	
	<PrisonLabor_Treatment.label>Treatment system</PrisonLabor_Treatment.label>
	<PrisonLabor_Treatment.helpText>In prison labor you need to take care for prisoners. Good treatment can prevent revolts, and can provoke recruit proposition (without recruting process!).\n\nTo maintain good treatment status you need to feed prisoners regularly and set some free time so they can regenerate their strength\n\nTreatment will go lower if you beat prisoners, starve them, or exploit in terms of labor.\nGood treatment will result in:\n - Random offers with request to join colony\n - Preventing revolts\n - Preventing suicide</PrisonLabor_Treatment.helpText>
</LanguageData>