<NewsFeed>
  <!-- How to insert news: -->
  <!-- [subtitle] for subtitle -->
  <!-- [img] ... [/img] for image (inside name of file) -->
  <!-- [gap] for gap -->
  <patches>
      <patch version="1.3.5" silent="true"/>
      <patch version="1.3.4" silent="true"/>
      <patch version="1.3.3" silent="true"/>
      <patch version="1.3.2" silent="true"/>
      <patch version="1.3.0" silent ="false">
          <title>Prison Labor v 1.3.0</title>
          <items>
              <item>[-] Update to Rimworld 1.3</item>
              <item>[-] Created menu for prisoners.</item>
              <item>[-] Created tab in prisoners menu "Overview". In this tab interaction mode can be chosen, resocialization offer is moved here from pawn prisoner tab. Also, possibility to order removing/putting cuffs on prisoners are here. Motivation level is also displayed here.</item>
              <item>[-] Created tab in prisoner menu "Work". It was moved from the tab "Work" in main tab.</item>
              <item>[-] Created tab in prisoner menu "Schedule". It was moved from the tab "Schedule" in  main tab.</item>
              <item>[-] Created tab in prisoner menu "Assign". Allows to assign diet and what kind of medicine should be used for prisoner.</item>
              <item>[-] Created tab in prisoner menu "Dev". For dev tools.</item>
              <item>[-] Moved restrict bill to group from drop down button to vanilla drop down pawn restriction in bill menu. Added new options to handle vanilla slaves.</item>
              <item>[gap]</item>
              <item>Some tutorials are now out of date. Hope to fix them soon.</item>
              <item>[gap]</item>
              <item>Honestly don't know if it will work correctly, didn't have enough time to test it right. Please report any bugs and not working slaves.</item>             
          </items>
      </patch>
      <patch version="1.2.5" silent ="false">
          <title>Prison Labor v 1.2.5</title>
          <items>
              <item>[-]Refactored rendering icons on prisoners. Instead of drawing textures, mesh is used. It may help with gray screen issue. Icons will be smaller now.</item>
              <item>[-]Various fixes to work patches which should reduce situations when prisoners stuck.</item>
              <item>[gap]</item>
              <item>Probably it is the last release for Rimworld version 1.2. Future updates will be pushed with version 1.3</item>
          </items>
      </patch>
      <patch version="1.2.4">
          <title>Prison Labor v 1.2.4</title>
          <items>
              <item>[-]Changed adding designer for prisoner labor zone to more "common" way. It may fix missing designators as mod incompatibility</item>
              <item>[-]Prisoners should respect their food restriction when motivation is more than 75%, or they are watched</item>
              <item>[-]Prisoners should use ground penetration and long scanners</item>
          </items>
      </patch>
    <patch version="1.0.3" silent="true"/>
    <patch version="1.0.2" silent="true"/>
    <patch version="1.0.1" silent="true"/>
    <patch version="1.0.0" silent="true"/>
    <patch version="0.10.1" silent="false">
      <title>Prison Labor v0.10.1</title>
      <items>
        <item>This patch contains a lot of changes, so there can be bugs. Please [b]report bugs[/b] so I can repair them ASAP</item>
        <item>[gap]</item>
        
        <item>[b]Treatment system[/b]</item>
        <item>[-]added new hidden need "Treatment" that indicates level of prison treatment towards prisoner</item>
        <item>[-]prisoners will now give offer to join colony if treatment is good enough (random)</item>
        <item>[-]prisoners now will pick up weapons if treated bad</item>
        <item>[-]added +5 bonus to mood while prisoner have free time</item>
        <item>[-]added +5 bonus to mood if prisoner is not supervised and got lazy</item>
        <item>[-]added +15 bonus to mood if treatment is above 75%</item>
        <item>[-]added prisoner suicides</item>
        <item>[-]added blocking revolts (100%, 95%, 50%, 10%) if overall prisoner treatment is good enough</item>
        <item>[-]added treatment drop when prisoner is being beaten</item>
        <item>[-]increased base chance for Revolts</item>
        <item>[-]added blocking mental breaks for prisoners with low treatment levels</item>
        <item>[-]"Treatment happiness" will decrease if health conditions are bad, when prisoners are hungry, or they're working.</item>

        <item>[b]Prisoners can do construction jobs now[/b]</item>

        <item>[b]Enchantments[/b]</item>
        <item>[-]new system for removing mod from save (new button in mod menu)</item>
        <item>[-]prisoners will now seek safe temperature when not supervised</item>
        <item>[-]prisoners will respect forbidden items, if "inspired"</item>
        <item>[-]prisoners will now work in cold only if "work" time is set</item>
        <item>[-]added alert when prisoners can escape</item>
        <item>[-]reworked news popup window</item>
        <item>[-]wardens no longer deliver food if prisoners can get it from another room</item>
        <item>[-]cosmetic changes to bill checkbox</item>
        <item>[-]prisoners will now stay at bed if waiting for surgery</item>

        <item>[b]Bugs[/b]</item>
        <item>[-]fixed food reservation throwing errors</item>
        <item>[-]fixed cutting some content of bill config in some languages</item>
        <item>[-]now work settings reset after prisoner is recruited, so it should fix some issues</item>
        <item>[-]finally fixed "OnGui()" error, big thanks to @notfood (https://github.com/notfood)</item>
        <item>[-]fixed blurred effect on settings window</item>
        <item>[-]fixed Revolts</item>

        <item>[gap]</item>

        <item>If you want to support the work I do, please consider small donation. Link to Ko-fi will be placed at steam page.</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.9.11">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.9.11</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]fixed compatibility with Fluffy's WorkTab (final)</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.9.10">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.9.10</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]hotfixed compatibility with Fluffy's WorkTab (still have some visual flaws)</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.9.9">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.9.9</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]added sub-tabs in \"Work\" Tab and \"Assign\" Tab for \"Colonists\" and \"Prisoners\"</item>
        <item>[-]added renaming Prisoners for imprisonment time (pawns will restore old names after releasing)</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.9.8">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.9.8</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]fixed SeedsPlease compatibility</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.9.7">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.9.7</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]added warning message before placing labor area for the first time</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.9.6">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.9.6</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]updated to RimWorld 1.0</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.9.5">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.9.5</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]updated to RimWorld Beta 19</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.9.4">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.9.4</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]disabled Warden and Jailor types of work for prisoner labor, it should fix bug, where jailors do not warden inside labor area</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.9.3">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.9.3</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]fixed compatibility with No Water no Life</item>
        <item>[-]fixed compatibility with Dubs Bad Hygiene Mod</item>
        <item>[-]fixed error with loading old saves</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.9.2">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.9.2</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]fixed seeds please compatibility issue</item>
        <item>[-]added option to disable revolts</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.9.1">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.9.1</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]changed max. skill required for non-advanced growing by prisoners to 6 instead of 0</item>
        <item>[-]added new work type Jailor</item>
        <item>[-]fixed drawing icons on world map</item>
        <item>[-]fixed disabling mod from existing saves</item>
        <item>[-]fixed incorrectly showing \"advanced growing by prisoners\" option</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.9.0">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.9.0</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]updated to RimWorld beta v18</item>
        <item>[-]added option to disable icons above prisoners heads in mod menu</item>
        <item>[-]fixed error \"null reference in onGui()\" when loading save</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.8.8">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.8.8</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]changed slow from prisoners chains to act as factor instead offset</item>
        <item>[-]fixed compatibility issues with Seeds Please(again)</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.8.7">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.8.7</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]fixed bug with dropping motivation while in bed</item>
        <item>[-]prisoners will now get different weapons when revolt triggers (molotovs, bows, or clubs)</item>
        <item>[-]replaced orginal jobs with \"tweak\" jobs (instead of overriding them, this fix is for users who use \"WorkTab\" by Fluffy)</item>
        <item>[-]removed warning message from logs</item>
        <item>[-]prisoners will now have 50% of normal speed in chains (instead of 35%)</item>
        <item>[-]prisoners will now break chains after some period of time instead of immadiately(matter in incidents, breakouts etc.)</item>
        <item>[-]wardens will now try to motivate most prisoners at once, but with priority to motivate lowest motivation first</item>
        <item>[-]fixed bug with animals do not respect reservations (and vice versa)</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.8.6">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.8.6</title>
      <items>
        <item>[img]NewsElement_Locks[/img][b]Locks mod:[/b]\nIf you want to allow prisoners to pass by closed doors, please check out my other mod called [b]Locks[/b]</item>
        <item>[gap]</item>
        <item>[-]fixed bug that Sowing job do not comply to Labor Area</item>
        <item>[-]fixed bug with JoyGiver debris (sorry about that)</item>
        <item>[-]reduced number of null reference errors with OnGui() method (fixed in v 0.8.5)</item>
        <item>[-]single warden will be able to maintain 7 prisoners, instead of 5 (because of laziness rate reduction) (changed in v 0.8.5)</item>
        <item>[-]decreased laziness rate to 0.002, instead of 0.003 (prisoners will get lazy 1.5x slower) (changed in v 0.8.5)</item>
        <item>[-]decreased manipulation to 70% (instead of 80%) (changed in v 0.8.5)</item>
        <item>[-]fixed null reference exception at loading game (fixed in v 0.8.4)</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.8.3">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.8.3</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]fixed bugs with disabling mod(now you can safely disable mod again)</item>
        <item>[-]fixed bug with prioritizing work</item>
        <item>[-]fixed bug with rendering icons on world map</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.8.1">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.8.1</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]fixed bug with rendering icons on world map</item>
        <item>[subtitle] If you encouter any bugs [b]please report it on github[/b]. I'm fixing most important ones every day. This is (recently) beta version and it has to consist some bugs. Thank you for understaning.</item>
        <item>[subtitle] Also you can always [b]download old version[/b] via github, but I think this was last big update</item>
        <item>[-]re-enabled button in Bills detail panel</item>
        <item>[-]added slider to Bills (temporary fix)</item>
        <item>[-]fixed Bill \"Prisoner only\" button (I think, let me know if you still experience errors)</item>
        <item>[-]fixed prisoners aren't working when Motivation is disabled (via Settings)</item>
        <item>[-]fixed null-reference error on some revolts incidents</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.8.0">
      <title>Prison Labor Beta v0.8.0</title>
      <items>
        <item>[subtitle][b]Now in Beta![/b] I would no longer add any more features. Instead I will focus on improving existing ones.</item>
        <item>[gap]</item>
        <item>[subtitle][b]Main changes:[/b]</item>
        <item>[img]NewsElement_Revolt[/img][b]Revolts:[/b]\nPrisoners will now form organized group under self-elected leader if motivation of prisoners is low. They will try to inflict damage to your colony or they will attemp running to elected enemy faction</item>
        <item>[img]NewsElement_InspirationReworked[/img][b]Insiration reworked:[/b]\nQuicker, better and more intuitive.\nYou can now send your prisoners to work outside your walls, but be carefull: they will try to escape if left alone. Prisoners will start thinking about escape after being left for some time.</item>
        <item>[img]LaborAreaExpand[/img][b]Labor area:[/b]\nYou can now select area for labor only. Your colonists will no longer go mine with peasants.\nTo access this tool look into \"Architect->Zones\" panel.</item>
        <item>[img]NewsElement_PrisonersOnly[/img][b]Prisoners Only button[/b]\nGo to Bill details to mark bills for prisoners only!</item>
        <item>[img]NewsElement_WorkAndRecruit[/img][b]Work and recruit:[/b]\nThis feature has been mostly requested by community. I hope it will be well received.</item>
        <item>[gap]</item>
        <item>[subtitle][b]Other changes:[/b]</item>
        <item>[-]added default prisoner interaction mode option to settings menu</item>
        <item>[-]added icons above prisoners indicating whenever he's being motivated/inspired</item>
        <item>[-]reduced manipulation capability of prisoners (now they have 80% of normal manipulation, down from 100%)</item>
        <item>[-]added tutorials triggers (now all tutorials will be shown)</item>
        <item>[-]added watched tutorials to properties (tutorials will no longer be shown after reenabling mod)</item>
        <item>[-]fixed forbidden bug with harvesting plants (again)</item>
        <item>[-]fixed Toil reservation bug (not respecting prisoners' job)</item>
        <item>[-]fixed compatibility with Dubs Hygiene Mod</item>
        <item>[-]fixed SeedsPlease compatibility</item>
        <item>[-]excluded supervising from labor</item>
        <item>[-]rewritten news dialog - now with images and stuff</item>
        <item>[-]perfomance and code improvements</item>
        <item>[-]translation improvements</item>
        <item>[gap]</item>
        <item>[subtitle]Also I want to annouce that I will start new mod called [b]Prison Expansion[/b] that would be PrisonExtensions remake.The aim of this mod would be improving Prison Labor experience, especially cell doors and fences.</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.7">
      <title>Prison Labor Alpha v0.7</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]Added settings! You can now change almost any aspect of this mod, including:\n   * work types\n   * motivation mechanics\n   * prevention of planting advanced plants.</item>
        <item>[-]Added \"uninstaller\" (\"disable\" option in settings), which will allow to disable this mod from existing saves.</item>
        <item>[-]\"No more beeping!\". Changed way of informing player what's going on with prisoners. It should be less annoying and more insightful.</item>
        <item>[-]Fixed bugs, including bug that prevents prisoners from cleaning and bug that causes warden to stuck in loop of delivering food to prisoner.</item>
        <item>[-]\"No more watching while prisoner is sleeping.\"Wardens will no longer watch over not working prisoners.</item>
        <item>[-]Prisoners will now stay in bed while waiting for operation</item>
        <item>[-]Prisoners will now stop work when starving for default (\"Anything\" time), instead of hungry. They will still get minor debuff.</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.6">
      <title>Prison Labor Alpha v0.6</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]Time restrictions - now you can manage your prisoners time for sleep, work and joy. You can now even force them to work when they're hungry!</item>
        <item>[-]Getting food by prisoners - Now prisoners will look for food in much better way, and now (when they desperate enough) they will eat corpses!</item>
        <item>[-]\"Laziness\" changed to \"Motivation\" and inverted.\n\n   ATTENTION: After PrisonLabor reaches beta all saves with PrisonLabor v0.5a or lower will be corrupted and unplayable. This version (0.6) is safe and converts all older saves.</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
    <patch version="0.5">
      <title>Prison Labor Alpha v0.5</title>
      <items>
        <item>[-]Prisoners can now grow, but only plants that not require any skills.</item>
        <item>[-]You can now manage prisoners work types. Just check \"Work\" tab!</item>
        <item>[-]Laziness now appear on \"Needs\" tab. Above 50% wardens will watch prisoners. Above 80% prisoners won't work unless supervised.</item>
        <item>[-]Wardens will now bring food to prisoners that went too far from his bed.</item>
        <item>[-]Prisoners won't gain laziness when not working anymore.</item>
        <item>[-]Fixed many bugs</item>
      </items>
    </patch>
  </patches>
</NewsFeed>


