<TutorialFeed>
  <!-- How to insert rich text: -->
  <!-- [subtitle] for subtitle -->
  <!-- [img] ... [/img] for image (inside name of file) -->
  <!-- [gap] for gap -->
  <tutorials>
    <tutorial key="Introduction">
      <items>
        <item>[title]Prison Labor Mod - Introduction</item>
        <item>Are you new to Prison Labor Mod? Don't worry, in this tutorial you will learn how to use this mod.</item>
        <item>The main goal of this mod is to make prisoners work, but managing prisoners is challenge on it's own, so let's go with tutorial ...</item>
        <item>[title]Enabling labor for prisoners</item>
        <item>There are two main things you need to do before prisoners start working:</item>
        <item>[img]Tutorials/ForceToWork[/img]1. Firstly, you need to enable labor in <b>Prisoner</b> tab</item>
        <item>[gap]</item>
        <item>[img]Tutorials/WorkTab[/img]2. Then you need to adjust work priorities in work tab. There is a special sub-tab in top of <b>Work</b> tab</item>
        <item>There are a limited number of available jobs for prisoners. Additionally, you can change that in setting menu, but not all jobs are well implemented and you can experience weird behaviour by doing so.</item>
        <item>[title]Motivation</item>
        <item>Prisoners are not colonists and they do not want to work on their own. You need to motivate them and watch them constantly.</item>
        <item>[img]Tutorials/InspirationPreview[/img]To watch prisoners, colonists must be within a 10-meter radius of the prisoner (and vice-versa). Prisoners that are near colonists will work and gain motivation. Additionally, prisoners do not escape if colonists are nearby, but they can take a chance when nobody is watching them. It is worth noting that watching prisoners require the colonist and prisoner to be in same room.</item>
        <item>Watching prisoners can be done manually (drafting colonists) or by enabling the new work type <b>Jailor</b>.</item>
        <item>[title]Designing a Prison Encampment</item>
        <item>There are few things that you should keep in mind while building a prison:</item>
        <item>[-]Walls: Prisoners want to escape, so make sure they cannot open doors that lead into open spaces.</item>
        <item>[-]Accessing resources: If you want prisoners to refine materials (e.g. cooking), make sure they can access the required materials (e.g. meat or potatoes).</item>
        <item>[-]Accessing food: Prisoners should have access to food, like a fridge or food stockpiles. In Prison Labor mod, prisoners can take care of themselves and go for a food run if you let them.</item>
        <item>[-]Labor Areas: These areas are optional, but in some cases you may want to keep colonists from working inside your prison. That's where Labor Areas comes in. They prevent colonists from working inside this area.</item>        <item>[title]Icons</item>
        <item>[img]Tutorials/Icons[/img]There are three icons in mod. Inspiration icon (blue one) - that indicates whenever prisoner is motivated by a standing colonist, Lazy icon (red one) - that indicates whenever a prisoner is too lazy to work, Freezing Icon - that indicates prisoner is working despite freezing temperature.</item>
        <item>[title]Locks Mod</item>
        <item>[img]NewsElement_Locks[/img]I highly recommend using <b>Locks</b> mod. It allows you to make doors passable by prisoners without making them use force to open.</item>
        <item><b>If you have any questions please visit the FAQ first</b></item>
      </items>
    </tutorial>
    <tutorial key ="LaborArea">
      <items>
        <item>[title]Labor Areas</item>
        <item>Labor Areas aren't required to make prisoners work.</item>
        <item>This area forbids colonists from working.</item>
        <item>It's for situations where you don't want colonists to work in certain area. Prisoners will work anywhere they can enter.</item>
      </items>
    </tutorial>
  </tutorials>
</TutorialFeed>
